<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SourceBans&#43;&#43;</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on SourceBans&#43;&#43;</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 17:48:49 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1.6.3 Release 🔖</title><link>/blog/1.6.3_release/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 10:08:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>/blog/1.6.3_release/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s new ✨ Plugins
+ Discord: Listens for SBPP_OnBanPlayer() and the new SBPP_OnReportPlayer() natives and forwards it to the designated Discord webhook with PR #420
+ Report: Uses the new SBPP_ReportPlayer() to insert reports into the submissions table, reachable via Admin Panel -&amp;gt; Bans -&amp;gt; Ban submissions with PR #408 closing #407
Main: Now whenever a banned client joins, it will mend the IP column with the corresponding value if the column is previously empty with PR #406 closing issue #187</description></item><item><title>New Site</title><link>/blog/intro/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 23:31:41 -0500</pubDate><guid>/blog/intro/</guid><description>New Site Welcome to the new SourceBans++ site, this site is meant to serve as a replacement to the old one, featuring a brand new documentation, and FAQ pages</description></item><item><title>Quickstart</title><link>/docs/quickstart/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 20:47:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/quickstart/</guid><description>Prerequisites Before we get started, let&amp;rsquo;s make sure you meet these following requirements:
Web
A working MySQL/MariaDB database
PHP Version &amp;gt;= 5.6 (and PHP Version &amp;lt; 7.4 for SB++ 1.6.3 release)
GMP extension (for A2S queries)
Game
Sourcemod &amp;gt;= 1.7
Metamod: Source
If you&amp;rsquo;re using Cloudflare, Rocket Loader must be disabled otherwise SourceBans++ will become unresponsive.
Uploading Download the latest release from the release page</description></item><item><title>Inquiries</title><link>/docs/inquiries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 14:08:08 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/inquiries/</guid><description>Plugin Ban player option is missing in SourceMod&amp;rsquo;s admin menu! Most likely SourceMod&amp;rsquo;s basebans.smx was still loaded when you installed SourceBans&amp;rsquo; game plugin. The game plugin automatically disables basebans.smx, but your server needs to be restarted for the &amp;ldquo;Ban player&amp;rdquo; option to come available.
Some hosters might disallow plugins to move files. Make sure the basebans.smx is in the plugins/disabled folder.
Web Player list displays &amp;ldquo;Max Players&amp;rdquo; instead of all the players Add host_players_show 2 to your server.</description></item><item><title>Updating</title><link>/docs/updating/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 15:49:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/updating/</guid><description>Downloading Download the latest zip-archive from the release page
Web Panel Backup your database in case of corruption
Switch back to the default theme if haven&amp;rsquo;t already
Upload and overwrite all contents in web to your SourceBans++ installation
Delete install directory
Navigate to your SourceBans++ website and append updater after it (Ex: example.com/updater, example.com/sb/updater)
After it displays Installation up-to-date., delete updater directory and you are done</description></item><item><title>Discord Forward Setup</title><link>/docs/discord_forward_setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 17:48:49 -0400</pubDate><guid>/docs/discord_forward_setup/</guid><description>Prerequisites SteamWorks SMJansson Installing Grab the latest sbpp_discord.smx from here
Upload the plugin to addons/sourcemod/plugins
Configuring Add the convar sbpp_discord_banhook and assign the value of the Discord webhook link for where you want ban messages to go
Add the convar sbpp_discord_reporthook and assign the value of the Discord webhook link for where you want report messages to go (If missing, it will default to sbpp_discord_banhook&amp;rsquo;s convar value)</description></item><item><title>Database Errors</title><link>/docs/database_errors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 11:52:38 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/database_errors/</guid><description>Access Denied If not self-hosted, please make sure your host allows remote connections This problem is often related to user accounts that the server permits
View MariaDB #Granting for more info
Can&amp;rsquo;t connect to MySQL server Normally means that there is no MySQL server running on the system or that you are using an incorrect Unix socket file name or TCP/IP port number when trying to connect to the server.</description></item><item><title>Debugging Connection</title><link>/docs/debugging_connection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 20:04:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/debugging_connection/</guid><description>Check list Your host is not blocking any traffic on your game server port (UDP Incoming &amp;amp; TCP Outgoing)
Your game server is online to people outside of your network w/o any error on binding
You can connect to server in-game
You can use RCON through in-game console, if not view TCP Error below
Using the debug tool In SourceBans++&amp;rsquo;s root directory, there&amp;rsquo;s a connection debug tool named sb_debug_connection.</description></item><item><title>MariaDB</title><link>/docs/mariadb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 20:30:47 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/mariadb/</guid><description>Adding Repo sudo apt-get install software-properties-common sudo apt-key adv --recv-keys --keyserver hkp://keyserver.ubuntu.com:80 0xF1656F24C74CD1D8 sudo add-apt-repository &#39;deb [arch=amd64,i386,ppc64el] http://nyc2.mirrors.digitalocean.com/mariadb/repo/10.2/ubuntu xenial main&#39; sudo apt-get update Installing sudo apt-get install mariadb-server Setup Run mysql_secure_installation
Configuring Navigate to your MariaDB config (Ex: /etc/mysql/mariadb.conf.d/50-server.cnf)
Comment out bind-address by prefixing it with a #, so it looks like #bind-address = 127.0.0.1
Restart MySQL via sudo systemctl restart mysql
Granting Permission Sign in to MySQL shell via sudo mysql -u root -p and enter your password</description></item><item><title>Adding Server</title><link>/docs/adding_server/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 15:27:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/adding_server/</guid><description>Adding server to web panel Navigate to Admin Panel -&amp;gt; Server Settings -&amp;gt; Add new server
Fill out the information about the server with correct RCON Password and click Add Server when done
On refresh, record down the ID column for the corresponding server
Configuring SourceBans++&amp;rsquo;s ServerID Navigate to addons/sourcemod/configs/sourcebans
Edit sourcebans.cfg and modify ServerID to the ID value you recorded down</description></item><item><title>Could not find driver &#34;MySQL&#34;</title><link>/docs/could_not_find_driver/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 21:56:16 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/could_not_find_driver/</guid><description>Web Ensure you have installed the mysql extension of your PHP version (Ex: php7.2-mysql) Ensure pdo_mysql module is loaded, check phpinfo() for this Plugin Please make sure dbi.mysql.ext.so (dbi.mysql.ext.dll on Windows) extension exists and check if it is loaded via sm exts list
Make sure the extension is executable via chmod u+x dbi.mysql.ext.so
Install zlib (Requires SSH Access)
32-Bit Debian/Ubuntu: apt-get install zlib1g</description></item><item><title>Removing Default Message</title><link>/docs/removing_default_message/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 21:52:44 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/removing_default_message/</guid><description> Removal Navigate to Admin Panel -&amp;gt; Webpanel Settings
Edit the Intro Text
Save Changes and you are done</description></item><item><title>Ports</title><link>/docs/ports/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 21:47:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/ports/</guid><description> Web Panel UDP Incoming on game server port
TCP Outgoing on game server port
Game Server Port ( UDP &amp;amp; TCP )</description></item><item><title>Translating</title><link>/docs/translating/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 11:58:42 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/translating/</guid><description>Web Panel Navigate to the root directory of your SourceBans++ installation&amp;rsquo;s themes folder
Make a copy of the default theme, rename it to a name of your choosing and navigate to it
Modify theme.conf.php to reflect the configuration and save
&amp;lt;?php // Set the name of this theme here define(&#39;theme_name&#39;, &amp;quot;SourceBans++ Default Theme&amp;quot;); // Set the author of this theme here define(&#39;theme_author&#39;, &amp;quot;IceMan, SourceBans++ Dev Team&amp;quot;); // Set the version of the theme here define(&#39;theme_version&#39;, &amp;quot;1.</description></item><item><title>Browser Freeze</title><link>/docs/browser_freeze/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 11:34:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/browser_freeze/</guid><description>Cloudflare If your site uses Cloudflare as reverse-proxy, make sure that Rocket Loader is off
Rocket Loader bundles mootools incorrect and cause unnecessary loop calls
Debugging Most browsers bundles with a performance debugger, typically accessible via the hotkey F12
With the performance recorder open, start recording, navigate to the unresponsive page, end the recording after ~10 seconds and export it
Join our Discord guild and post in #help-support with the exported performance file attached</description></item></channel></rss>